{
  "id": 301,
  "themeId": 3,
  "name": "Writing and Reading Numbers Test 1",
  "description": "Autogenerated quiz",
  "version": "2.2.1",
  "lastUpdated": "13/04/2025",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "How do you say “10”?",
      "options": [
        "Dix",
        "Dis",
        "Dixe",
        "All of the above"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Dix",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you say “99”?",
      "options": [
        "Quatrevingtdixneuf",
        "Quatre vingt-dix-neuf",
        "Quatre-vingt-dix-neuf",
        "Quatre vingt dix neufs"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Quatre-vingt-dix-neuf",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you say “150”?",
      "options": [
        "Cent-cinquantes",
        "Cents-cinquante",
        "Cents cinquantes",
        "Cent-cinquante"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Cent-cinquante",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you say “100 000”?",
      "options": [
        "Cent-mille",
        "Cents-milles",
        "Cents-mile",
        "Cent-miles"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Cent-mille",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you say “7 millions”?",
      "options": [
        "Sept million",
        "Sept millions",
        "Septs millions",
        "Septs million"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Sept millions",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you say \"80\"?",
      "options": [
        "Quatre-vingts",
        "Quatres-vingts",
        "Quatreu-vingts",
        "Quatre-vingtes"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Quatre-vingts",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you say \"5 billion\"?",
      "options": [
        "Cinq milliars",
        "Cinq milliardes",
        "Cinqs milliard",
        "Cinq milliards"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Cinq milliards",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you say \"25%\"?",
      "options": [
        "Vingt-cinq pour cents",
        "Vingt-cinq pour cent",
        "Vingt-cinqs pour cents",
        "Vingts-cinq pour cents"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Vingt-cinq pour cent",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you say \"200 ou 210 euros\"?",
      "options": [
        "Deux cents ou deux-cent-dix euros ?",
        "Deux cent ou deux-cent-dix euros ?",
        "Deux cents ou deux-cents-dix euros ?",
        "Deux cents ou deux-cents-dix euro ?"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Deux cents ou deux-cent-dix euros ?",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you say \"les 12 coups de minuit\" ?",
      "options": [
        "les drouze coups de minuit",
        "Les douze coups de minuit",
        "les douces coups de minuit",
        "les douzze coups de minuit"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Les douze coups de minuit",
      "explanation": ""
    }
  ]
}